DiagnosticTestsQuestions = [
    {
        "question": "The fishbone diagram includes values such as e____, l____, p____, E____S____R____",
        "answer": "erythrocytes, leukocytes, platelets, erythrocytes sedimentation rate",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The hemoglobin values for males is ____-____g/dL and the values for women is ____-____g/dL",
        "answer": "14-17.5, 12.3-15.3",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The normal mean cell volume is ____fL",
        "answer": "75-100",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Microcytic anemia such as ____ deficiency is MCV value <____fL",
        "answer": "iron, 75",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Macrocytic anemia such as vitamin ____ or f____ acid deficiency is MCV values >____",
        "answer": "B12, folic, 100",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The normal white blood cell value is ____-____x10^3/mm^3 or ____-____mm^3 or ____-____x10^9/L or ____-____x10^3/uL",
        "answer": "5-10, 5000-10000, 5-10, 5-10",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The most abundant leukocytes to least is ordered n____, l____, m____, e____, b____ (Never Let Monkeys Eat Banana)",
        "answer": "neutrophil, lymphocyte, monocyte, eosinophil, basophil",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Agranulocytes are l____ and m____",
        "answer": "lymphocyte, monocyte",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Neutrophils are the most abundant WBC and are increased during bacterial or fungal infections. The absolute neutrophil count is calculated as ANC= ____(____mature +____immature)",
        "answer": "WBC, SEG, bands",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "ANC predicts the body's defense against infection. The normal range of ANC is ____-____ cells/mm^3",
        "answer": "1500-8000",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Agranulocytosis is when ANC <____ cells/mm^3 and is also known as absolute n____ and there is a h____ risk of infection",
        "answer": "500, neutropenia, high",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "ANC is used to monitor patients undergoing c____ or patients taking medication such as c____",
		"answer": "chemotherapy, clozapine",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Neutrophilia occurs when there are i____ neutrophils and bands and this indicates a response to i____ cytokines and production of large number of new and immature white blood cells trying to fight off an infection",
        "answer": "increased, inflammatory",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "neutrophilia value >____ indicates possible causes of b____ infection, or medication induced from l____ and/or s____",
        "answer": "12000, bacterial, lithium, steroids",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Neutropenia values <____ indicate possible causes such as r____ exposure, c____, or overwhelming acute b____ infection",
        "answer": "1500, radiation, chemotherapy, bacterial",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "lymphocytosis >____ indicate possible causes such as v____ infection or l____",
        "answer": "4000, viral, lymphoma",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lymphocytopenia <____ indicates possible causes such as H____ infection",
        "answer": "1000, HIV",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Eosinophilia values >____ indicates possible causes such as a____ reaction/disorder or p____ infection",
        "answer": "350, allergic, parasitic",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Eosinopenia values <____ indicate possible causes such as a____ infection",
        "answer": "50, acute",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Platelets normal range is ____-____/uL",
        "answer": "150,000-450,000",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The average life span of platelets is ____-____ days and there is a ____% turnover each day",
        "answer": "8-10, 10",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The function of platelets is to convert l____ blood into g____(clot) and this prevents bleeding by binding to site of damaged vessel",
        "answer": "liquid, gel",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Platelet aggregation can cause t____ formation and increase the risk of b____ clots, s____, h____ attack",
        "answer": "thrombus, blood, stroke, heart",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "thrombocytopenia is l____ platelet count <____/uL and some causes are d____ induced, i____ condition, c____ treatment",
        "answer": "low, 15000, drug, inherited, cancer",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one is not a sign/symptom of thrombocytopenia",
		"choices": "ecchymosis (discoloration of skin due to bleeding/bruising), petechiae (tiny round purple spots due bleeding under skin), hematuria(blood in urine), melena (dark tarry stool with or without blood), menorrhagia (heavy vaginal bleeding), epistaxis (nose bleed), bleeding gums, shortened bleeding",
        "answer": "shortened bleeding",
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "question": "thrombocytosis is also known as t____ has platelet counts > ____/uL and some causes are s____, i____, s____, posthemorrhagic a____",
		"answer": "thrombocythemia, 800000, stress, infection, splenectomy, anemia",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The erythrocyte sedimentation rate is useful for monitoring i____ conditions and is higher when d____ is active",
        "answer": "inflammatory, disease",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Serum creatinine levels range from ____-____mg/dL and creatine is produced in the l____ and filtered at the g____ and is a primary marker of r____ function",
        "answer": "0.6-1.2, liver, glomerulus, renal",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Serum creatinine should be avoided as the s____ assessment of renal function",
        "answer": "sole",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of the factors does not affect serum creatinine",
		"choices": "age, muscle mass, sex, race, diet, adipose mass",
        "answer": "adipose mass",
        "type": "multiple"
	},
    {
        "question": "The normal blood urea nitrogen range is ____-____mg/dL and is the e____ product of metabolism",
        "answer": "10-20, end",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "BUN is produced by the l____ and excreted by the k____",
        "answer": "liver, kidneys",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Elevated BUN is caused by h____ protein diet/catabolism, GI bleeding where blood in the gut is converted to a____ and u____ nitrogen, r____ renal blood flow (dehydration)",
        "answer": "high, ammonia, urea, reduced",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Decreased BUN is caused by m____ or s____ liver damage",
        "answer": "malnutrition, severe",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "BUN and serum creatinine levels are similar because they are both filtered by the g____ and they are different because urea is reabsorbed by t____ whereas c____ is m____ reabsorbed",
        "answer": "glomerulus, tubules, creatinine, minimally",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": ">20:1 BUN:Cr indicates BUN reabsorption is i____, BUN is disproportionately e____ relative to creatinine and d____ is suspected",
        "answer": "increased, elevated, dehydration",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "10:1 or 20:1 ratio is n____ range and reabsorption is within normal limits",
        "answer": "normal",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "<10:1 ratio is due to r____ damage which causes r____ reabsorption of BUN",
        "answer": "renal, reduced",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "The normal range of CrCl is ____-____ mL/min and provides a good approximation of G____",
        "answer": "90-140, GFR",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Two methods to calculate CrCl is by c____ or by estimating through C____-G____ equation",
        "answer": "calculating, Cockcroft-Gault",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ideal body weight is calculated in females as ____ + (2.3 kg x inches over 5' and in males as ____ + (2.3 kg x inches over 5') ",
		"answer": "45.5, 50",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "the adjusted body weight is calculated as ABW= 0.4 (____-____) + IBW",
        "answer": "ABW, IBW",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Acute kidney failure occurs when",
		"choices": "increase in SCr by >= 0.3 mg/dL within 48 hours, increase in SCr of 1.5 times or more the patient's baseline within the past week, urine volume <0.5 mL/kg/hour for > 6 consecutive hours, all of the above, none of the above",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to Kidney Disease Outcome Quality Initiative chronic kidney disease is",
		"choices": "kidney damage for more than 3 months +/- decreased GFR, GFR less than GFR 60mL/min/1.73 m^2 for 3 months, abnormalities in blood or urine, abnormalities in imaging tests, all of the above, none of the above",
        "answer": "all of the above",
        "type": "multiple"
    },
    {
        "question": "Risk factors for CKD (DM, HTN, family history) lead to i____ risk of developing kidney disease",
        "answer": "increased",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Kidney damage with normal GFR leads to stage ____ CKD",
        "answer": "1",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Kidney damage with mild GFR leads to stage ____ CKD",
        "answer": "2",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Moderate decrease in GFR leads to stage ____ CKD",
        "answer": "3",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Severe decrease in GFR leads to stage ____",
        "answer": "4",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Kidney failure is stage ____",
        "answer": "5",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "Albuminura/proteinuria h____ albumin/protein is a m____ of kidney damage (nephropathy), p____ factor, and c____ risk factors",
        "answer": "high, marker, progression, cardiovascular",
        "type": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "A patient can be screened for albuminuria if they have excretion >____ mcg/mg",
        "answer": "30",
        "type": "fill"
    }
]